我们要做的第四个项目
Okay, so this fourth and final project
也是我们最后一个项目
that we'll work on together is
是我心目中最酷
in my opinion the coolest
也是最有趣的一个
and was the most fun to work on.
非常有爱的漫威公司提供了API
Marvel was kind enough to allow us
供我们在本期教学中使用
to use their API in this tutorial series,
我们用它来创建一个炫酷的例子
and build a really cool example
来帮助我们学习开发
to help us all learn development,
学习使用漫威的API接口
learn development against the Marvel API.
所以我将会给你演示如何在他们的网站注册账号
So we'll show you how to create an account on their site
以及如何去使用他们的交互式文档
and how to use their interactive documentation
来学习如何去调用接口，获取信息
to learn how to make calls and get information back,
当然还有获取他们的图片然后处理它们
how to retrieve their images and work with them as well.
所以我们来创建一个应用
So we're building an application
我们叫它 --英雄图鉴--
that I call the Hero Explorer,
首先，它可以让你获取
rand it allows you to, first of all,
一些动漫人物的随机集合
just get a random collection of characters
来源就是漫威的数据库，我想大约有超过1500个人物
from their database of, I think over 1500 characters.
现在我们就，从左侧栏中的列表里
And so we're just going to like, select one of the characters
通过点击选择一个人物
by clicking in a master list on the left-hand side
来查看这个人物的详情
to view the details about that character
详情页在右边栏中
on the right-hand side.
让我看看，并不是所有人物都有全部的信息
So let me find, not all characters have all information,
一些经典的人物会有一个名字
but typically characters will have a name
名字下一个简单的描述
and a description below them,
一个大的图片，以及...
a large image, and then also
他们最近出演的所有的本子(●'◡'●)
the comic books that they've been in recently,
通过点击其中一个
and then clicking on one of those
会显示本子的名字
will show you the name of the comic,
实际上是标题
or actually the title,
和特定期号内容的简介
and then the description of that particular issue.
通过这个例子
And so there's a bunch of stuff that we're going to learn
有一大堆东西我们要去学习
by going through this example.
首先我们去学习如何去调用
First of all, we're going to learn how to call
一个公共的API，一个web API
a public API, web API,
解析文档的内容
interpret the documentation,
基于文档中的JSON例子创建类
create classes based on JSON examples in the documentation,
然后去解析（反序列化）我们请求到类中的
then de-serialize live data that we request
实时数据
into those classes.
我们将要去学习这其中的主要细节
We're going to learn this master detail
有点儿像用户体验设计的模式
kind of user design experience pattern,
我们还要去学习创建
and we're also going to learn how to create
和使用这些可适应布局的内容
and utilize some of the adaptive layout stuff
当前，这些内容之前已经学习过了
that we learned how to do earlier in this series of lessons.
我们要做成吨的数据绑定
We're going to do a ton of data binding
还要去解决很多现实中常遇到的问题
and working through real world issues
当你编写和这相似类型应用的时候
that you're going to probably experience
这些问题在也会不时出现
when building a similar style application.
你会注意到，在这里，我使用了
You'll notice that over here I'm using
圆形和一种特色的画刷
an Ellipse and a special brush,
不是SolidColorBrush，也不是GradientBrush,
not a SolidColorBrush, not a GradientBrush,
而是ImageBrush用来填充这个圆形
but an ImageBrush as the fill for that Ellipse.
我们要调用特殊的API
We're going to call special APIs
它具有一些特别的安全形式
that require some form of security.
在漫威的API中
So in the case of the Marvel API,
我们将去学习如何使用我们的公共API密钥
we're going to learn how to create a cache
以及私密API密钥来创建缓存
using our public API key and a private API key
还会使用一些时间戳值,来确保
and then some timestamp value to ensure that, well,
首先，要认证请求的合法性
to authenticate the request first of all,
然后还要检查客户端到服务器的请求
and then also ensure that nobody's tampered with the request
确保没人篡改了其中的内容
as they inspect it from the client to the server.
我们还要学习如何使用
And so we're going to learn how to employ
特殊的加密类
special cryptography classes
在我们的Windows统一平台上
in the Universal Windows Platform,
最后我们还要将Cortana整合进我们的应用中
and then finally we're going to integrate our application
告诉Cortana，说
with Cortana, and tell Cortana,
"小娜，刷新一下我应用中的人物"
say hey, Cortana, refresh the characters in our application
然后她就照我们说的做了
and we'll see it work
然后我们就会知道，区区一只小娜
and learn a little bit more about how easy it is
真TM容易搞定
to integrate Cortana.
好的，相信这过程会非常有趣
Okay, so this was so much fun,
真是一颗赛艇
so exciting to work on,
享受它吧
I hope you enjoy this.
我们下节课正式开始
We'll get started in the next lesson.
到时候见，ヾ(•ω•`)o
See you there, thanks.